(Penny:)One, two,
(Penny:)three, four, five.
(Penny:)No way.
(Howard:)That's your card, right?
(Penny:)Seven of clubs!
(Penny:)That is amazing!
(Sheldon:)It's not amazing.
(Sheldon:)All magic tricks are merely
a combination
(Sheldon:)of manipulation
and misdirection
(Sheldon:)with the occasional dwarf in
a box wiggling his feet.
(Howard:)Oh, really?
So how did I do it?
(Sheldon:)I don't care how you did it.
(Sheldon:)I have more important things
to think about.
(Sheldon:)Clearly, the cards
are marked.
(Howard:)I thought you had more important
things to think about.
(Howard:)I do.
You just happened
(Sheldon:)to have caught me
on a break.
(Sheldon:)Oh, let me see
those cards.
(Penny:)Big deal. Not knowing
(Penny:)is part of the fun.
"Not knowing is part
of the fun."
(Sheldon:)Was that the motto
of your community college?